开始
Mark.
玛尔斯·布莱克蒙和我的主要人物迈克尔·乔丹
Mars Blackmon here with my main man Michael Jordan.
迈克 是什么让你成为了全球最棒的球星？
Mike, what makes you the best player in the universe?
- 是勇猛的扣篮吗？  - 不是 玛尔斯
- Is it the vicious dunks? - No, Mars.
- 是这个发型吗？  - 不是 玛尔斯
-Is it the haircut? -No, Mars.
- 是这双鞋吗？  - 不是 玛尔斯
-Is it the shoes? -No, Mars.
天啊 一定是鞋子
Money, it's gotta be the shoes.
鞋子 鞋子 鞋子
Shoes. Shoes. Shoes. Shoes.
- 你确定不是鞋子吗？  - 我确定 玛尔斯
-You sure it's not the shoes? -I'm sure, Mars.
停！
Cut!
我的比赛成绩是我代言商品的最大背书
My game was my biggest endorsement.
我在球场上的表现 我对比赛的投入
What I did on the basketball court, my dedication to the game,
带来了其他这一切
led to all this other stuff.
相信我 如果我平均得分2分 拿下三个篮板球
Believe me, if I was averaging two points, three rebounds,